Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2000-125
  - AIDS Education Project Records, Series 3
    - Health Care Professionals (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Home Care Issues (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - HTLV-III testing (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Insurance issues (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Legal issues and services (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Medical research (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Organizations – misc. USA (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Organizations – Aide Suisse Contre le SIDA/AIDS-Hilfe Schweiz (Zurich, Switzerland) (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Organizations – AIDS Project Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Organizations – Gay Men's Health Crisis (New York City) (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Organizations – Mobilization Against AIDS (S. F.) (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Organizations – National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (New York and Washington, DC) (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Organizations – National Gay Rights Advocates (S.F.) (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Organizations – San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Organizations – Shanti Project (S.F.) (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Proposition 64 – "Larouche AIDS Quarantine Initiative" – California Nov. 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - No on 102 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Public Health Information Materials - Australia (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Public Health Information Materials - Europe (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Public Health Information Materials - Japan (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Public Health Materials – United States – Spanish Language (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Public Health Materials – United States – Misc. Languages (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Public Health Materials – United States – English Language (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Publications – misc. (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Religious Issues (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Substance abuse issues (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Television coverage (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Theatrical works (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Therapies - drugs (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Therapies – holistic/metaphysical (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - US Dept. of Health and Human Services – Public Health Service (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - University and College Events (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - University and College Policies (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Non-oxynol 9 – Viricidal agents (topical) (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Women and AIDS (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Records, Series 4
    - Photographs of GPU/GLAS doings, 1979- (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Pamphlets on safe-sex, men's health issues (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Gay men's health misc. pamphlets (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - AIDS blood test newspaper articles (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - GPU/GLAS archives project (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 3rd Annual Queer Latino/a Youth Conference (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - CPPC for Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Students (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - 1999 General Grant Application (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - GALA Week 1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Posters - inscribed (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - GLAS archives – Dec. 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - In the Life (newsletter of the West Coast Lesbian Collections, Oakland, CA) (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - WSLGSU stuff (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Team GLAS reunion night and mailing lists (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Mailing lists (ca. 1977) (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - GPU/GCC office records at University Archives – preliminary inventory (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University Lesbian and Gay Archives Project, correspondence, 1986- (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Women's Center and LGBCC retreat schedule (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Misc. GLAS papers (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Volunteer/employment resources (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Queer Resources (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - LGB Orientation events 1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - LGBCC 1998-98 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - GALA Summer Internship Applications 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - LGBCC historical (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - LGBCC employment opportunities (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Monday night flicks (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - National Coming Out Day 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - LGBCC stuff 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - LGB Ally materials (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - LGB Aly for DOS staff (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - RA training (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - LGBCC Director proposal (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - LGB working group (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - GALA internships 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - LGBCC 1996-97 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - LGB Programming 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Speaker's Bureau (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - PFLAG (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - LGBCC 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - LGBCC 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - LGBCC 1991-92 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - LGBCC 1993-94 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Markowski-Leach Scholarship Fund (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - LGB Program ideas (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - LGB Working Group background reading (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The GALAvanter 1992 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming 95 GALA (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Reunion Homecoming ‘96 GALA dinner (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - LGBCC 1992-93 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Women's Studies misc. pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - AIDS resources and manuals (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - "Changing Men" magazine (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Gay/Queer – related press and articles (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - STD/AIDS prevention reports (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "M" magazine (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Photographs (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Autographed mementos (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Stanford flyers (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Misc. off-campus (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Envelope of assorted condoms (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Issues of "Gay Sunshine" (gay lib newspaper) 1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Button: "Pass A.B. 1 The Agnos Gay Rights Bill" (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Articles:
      - "The ERA is a Moral Issue," Mormons for the ERA (Box 9)
      - "Are there Gay People in my Business/Guide to Job Discrimination" (Box 9)
      - "Harassment of Gays at MIT" (Box 9)
      - Bibliography: Gay and Lesbian Books (Box 9)
      - "Anti-Gay Violence and Victimization in the United States" (Box 9)
      - Bibliography: Adolescent homosexual books (Box 9)
      - Bibliography: "Homosexuality," Gay People and Gay Liberation Movement (Box 9)
      - Poetry by Michael Ramsey-Perez (Box 9)
      - 3 papers on pederasty (Box 9)
      - SWOPSI: Two Women Eye-To-Eye: Lesbian Visions in Literature (Box 9)
      - Workshops on Homophobia and Homosexuality for College Campuses (Box 9)
      - "Journey Across America," Walt Curtis (Box 9)
      - "Memorandum of Theological Advice," Lutheran Church (Box 9)
      - "Report of the Commission on Personal Privacy," California, Dec. 1982 (Box 9)
      - "Equal Access to Justice" (Box 9)
      - Professional Organizations Directory, NGTF (Box 9)
      - "Reaching Out to Someone with AIDS" (Box 9)
      - Lesbian Literature Catalog (Box 9)
      - Reporting on AIDS, by the Wall Street Journal (Box 9)
      - Gay People's Union at Stanford University (Box 9)
      - "The Politics of AIDS," Frontline (Box 9)
      - "Perversion or Subversion," Scott Brookie (Box 9)
      - "Report of a Study of the Ethics of Homosexuality," Lutheran Church (Box 9)
      - "Gay People at a Critical Crossroad: Assimilation or Affirmation," D. Kilhefner (Box 9)
      - "Chimerical Creatures" (Box 9)
      - "Step by Step, Day by Day," Rosa de la Vega (Box 9)
      - SWOPSI: Literary and Historical Applications to the Homosexual Experience (Box 9)
      - "Who's Behind the Gay Rights Movement" (Box 9)
      - "Homosexuality: Sexual Behavior of the Female Homosexual" (Box 9)
      - "NGTF Information and Reference Packet" California 1984 (Box 9)
      - "Fight for Lesbian and Gay Rights in the Age of AIDS and Reagan," Frontline (Box 9)
      - "Roy," by Roger Peyrefitte (Box 9)
      - Materials on Man/Boy love and related subjects (Box 9)
      - "Gay and Lesbian Bashing," Matt Rollefson (Box 9)
      - "Some Information for Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays," Helena M. Carlson (Box 9)
      - "Catastrophe Theory: A Topological Reconceptualization of Sexual Orientation" (Box 9)
      - "The Bible and Homosexuality," Boyce Hinman (Box 9)
      - 11th National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference (Box 9)
      - "Lesbians and Gays in the Military" (Box 9)
      - "Homosexuality and Ideological Strategies in the Art of Charles Demuth" (Box 9)
      - "Lesbian Herstory Archives News," Dec. 1981 (Box 9)
      - "Bi-Lingual Glossary of French Gay Male Slang," R. G. Koskovich (Box 9)
      - Volume II, Lesbian Studies (Box 9)
      - "Interview with Edouard Roditi," R. G. Koskovich (Box 9)
      - Gay Liberation Statue Report [Segal statue on campus] (Box 9)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2000-243
  - Gay & Lesbian Organizations – Stanford – misc. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advertisements – housing, personals, etc. from GLAS Bulletin Boards, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GLAS Community Service Award, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Events & Activities (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Personal correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Old calendars (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - LGBCC correspondence, flyers, internal documents (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Non-Stanford signs, posters (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Old LGBCC receipts (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - No on 64 (1986) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - National Condom Week, 14-21 Feb. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Education Project (1986-87) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dealings with S.O.S. (1986-87) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence – Stanford administrators (1986-87) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GLAS ASSU Account #7390 (fiscal year 86-87) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - G & L Peer Counseling Account #7391 (fiscal year 86-87) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - GALA & GAS (flyers, receipts, documents) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Other student groups outside Stanford, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Financial, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Phone/answering machine, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Steering Committee, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - March on Washington (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gay & Lesbian Awareness Week, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - GALA Receipts (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - GALA Week (1987-88) Acct. #7393 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Misc., 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Ehrman – Otero incident 6/88 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - GLBA (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Women's Collective, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Orientation 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Orientation meeting, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Fliers and pubs, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Segal sculpture correspondence (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence with other student G&L groups, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, general, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dealings with S.O.S., 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Administrative clerical post (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Planning for Com. Center SPR, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Reconstruction of Old Firehouse, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Firehouse reconstruction, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Gay & Lesbian Awareness Week – Press Publicity, May 1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Steering Committee Fall Q. 87 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - GLAS Steering Committee Winter Q, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Financial things, 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Response to Daily letter, 10 Nov. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Publication agreement, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - GLAS ASSU Acct #7390 (Fiscal Year 1987-88) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Women of GLAS ASSU Acct #7388 (Fiscal Year 1987-88) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - GALA Week 1986 Program Book (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - GALA Week 1986 events (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - GALA 1988 proofs (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - GALA Week 1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - GALA Week 1989 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - GALA Week 1987, miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - GALA Week Exhibit (May 1987) invitations, press release, other publicity (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - GALA Week 1987 – Exhibit at Walt Whitman Bookshop and Meyer Library (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - GALA Week 1986 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - GALA Week 1987 financial (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - GALA Week 1986 – program book, advertisements (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - S. Committee surveys 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Sala Week 1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Financial Information 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - G & L Peer Counseling FY 85-86 Acct. #7391 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Internal Communications – misc., 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - SOS 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - GLAS – December 1985 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - GLAS – Jan. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - GLAS – Feb. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - GLAS – March 1986 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - GLAS – April 1986 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - GLAS – ASSU ACCT #7390 FY 85-86 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - 7393 – GALA week (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - GLAS Dances 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Peninsula Lesbian/Gay Interest Survey (1983-86) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Office Computer (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Program Ideas (1985-86) (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Financial Statements (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Financial Records – refrigerator/refreshment receipts, 1984-86 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Potential funding organizations (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Meetings with President Kennedy (1986-87) (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Other student groups, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Stanford AIDS Education Project, misc. (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Rolodex and message board listings, retined, 1986-87 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Stanford Daily Magazine (24 Jan. 1986) – Homosexuality special issue (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - The Robby Perkins (1985) (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Meetings and correspondence with Dean Lyons, 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - GALA Week 1988 (prelims in 1987) (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Steering Committee 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Events tape 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Mike Hollars – treasurer manuals, guidelines, reports (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - 31291 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - 31321 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - 31352 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - 1984-85 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Women's Collective ACCT #7388 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Unsorted correspondence, notes, calendars, flyers, publications, and other items (foldered for convenience only – no order to box) (Box 2)
  - Unsorted correspondence, notes, calendars, flyers, publications, and other items (foldered for convenience only – no order to box) (Box 3)
  - Women's Collective Records (Box 3)
  - Unsorted correspondence, notes, calendars, flyers, publications, and other items (foldered for convenience only – no order to box) (Box 4)
  - Photographs (including Stanford group at 1979 national march in Washington, demo during 1991 talk by Gov. Pete Wilson, 1997 sit-in in White Plaza, and Segal statue work 1984) (Box 4)
  - Audiovisual material
    - Abortion Denied, 1990. by The Feminist Majority, Los Angeles., 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS Challenge: Stanford Symposium, 1986, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS in the Workplace (Pacific Bell) (Box 5)
    - AIDS Lifeline: KPIX Program, 1987. 2 copies, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS: People are Talking, 1987, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS PSAs: LA Cares, 1985, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS Test Program, National, 1987, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AIDS in Your School, ca. 1988, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - AmFar Video Teleconference, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Bug Bunny cartoon, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - C & C Music Factory, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Disappear Fear "Kiss the World", 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Felix the Cat cartoon, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Gay Topics: Pride, Prejudice and Gay Politics. KQED, 1982, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Lost Language of Cranes [apparently taped over Gays and Lesbian in the Residences (ResED)], 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - 1987 March on Washington (2 tapes), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Matthew Shepard vigil, 1998, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - NAMES Quilt Project, Inaugural display, 1987, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Out for the Count. 2 copies, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Parents Come Out; and Mandela. KQED, 1986, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Together Alone, by P. J. Castellaneta. A Frameline Release, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
    - Phone machine recording of a bomb threat to LGBCC, Fall 1991, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Unprocessed Newsprint (clippings and whole publications) (Box 6)
  - Posters from ACCN 2000-243:
    - Exhibition and slideshow by Lynda Koolish, The Evolution of Lesbian and Feminist Culture, 1988 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Women's Dance, Elliott Program Center, Friday July 21 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week, May 6-12, 1990 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - LCBCC general activities 1998 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Lesbians Pizza + Possibilities Tues. Oct 14 Old Firehouse (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Camera ready copy for brochure on the film "Living with AIDS" (2 pages) (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week Stanford University May 4-12, 1985 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Friendship, intimacy and sexuality in the age of AIDS [AIDS awareness week], 1989 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Peninsula Gay Pride Week Conference at Stanford University June 24-29 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - First Annual Queer Winter Ball [Stanford] Dec. 5, 1998 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Eroticizing Safer Sex; A Workshop for Gay and Bisexual Men, Thursday, April 9, Old Firehouse (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Camera ready copy for GLAS Weekly Events Summer Quarter 1986 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week Stanford University May 3-10, 1986 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - AIDS and Public Health: Are Current Measures Enough? Stanford Medical School Evening Forum, May 6, 1987 [handwritten addition: AIDS Quarantine?????] (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Jing Lyman Lectures Women Making Music Spring 1988 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 3-9 1987 Stanford University (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 7-12, 1984 Stanford University (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - AIDS Project of San Mateo County presents Hot and Health Sex, Feb. 5, 1987 (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 7-13, 1989 Stanford University (Box 7 os, Folder 1)
    - Stanford's Bisexual Gay Lesbian Awareness Days, 1999 (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 6-12, 1990, at Stanford University (signed by various people) (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Stanford's Bisexual Gay Lesbian Awareness Days, 1996 (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Women and Men: Voices for Change. Conference sponsored by Rape Education Project (S.U.) April 3-5, 1987 (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Lesbians who... copyright 1982 M. Lloyd (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights October 14, 1979 [note in ink: fours members of the Stanford community carried the "Gay People's Union at Stanford" banner in this march!] (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Three sheets of large paper with handwritten notes (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Poster (handmade): Stanford Daily article on Masque magazine pasted on blue paper with the photo colored in and decorated (Box 8 os, Folder 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 6-12, 1990, at Stanford University (mounted on board) (Box 8 os, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 7-15, 1982 Stanford University (mounted on board) (Box 8 os, Folder 2)
  - Posters from ACCN 2000-125:
    - Reception with Urvashi Vaid, Friday November 3rd [no year but prior to 1987] with photo of Vaid and LGBCC people; and Gay Awareness Week April 25-May 5, 1980 Stanford University (Box 7 os, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 7-12, 1984 Stanford University (mounted on board) (Box 7 os, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week Stanford University May 3-10, 1986 (mounted on board) (Box 7 os, Folder 2)
    - Bisexual, Gay and Lesbian Awareness Days Apr. 21-May 4, 1991, Stanford University (mounted on foam core) (Box 7 os, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week May 7-15, 1982 (mounted on board) (Box 7 os, Folder 2)
    - Poster (handmade): photographs from 1991 protest at Pete Wilson's talk, with an article from "The Firehouse Flame" (Box 8 os, Folder 3)
    - Black Liberation Month, Stanford University February 2000 (Box 8 os, Folder 3)
    - Stanford's Queer Awareness Days April 3-14, 2000 (3 copies) (Box 8 os, Folder 3)
    - 1993 March on Washington, with photographs of Stanford contingent (mounted on masonite) [from ACCN 2000-125] (Box 8 os)
- Additional Records, 1974-2004; Accession ARCH-2006-211
  - BGLAD records, 1992 (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - BGLAD records, 1992 (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BGLAD records, 1992 (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - BGLAD conference evaluation forms, [1998] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BGLAD conference evaluation forms, [1998] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "How To" book of office instructions, Spring 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous flyers, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous records, 2001, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous source materials (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Northern California Lesbian and Gay Community Center Regional Meeting, March 8, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Queer Awareness Days (QuAD), 2002, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford's LGBT history (on laminated sheets) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photo Album, 1996 and undated (Box 2)
  - Poster: National Coming Out Day. stanford lgbt community resources center. October 11, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Binder: Queer Issues Course Reader Winter Quarter 2000 (Box 2)
  - Binder: SWOPSI 169 Demystifying Homosexuality Syllabus and Readings Spring 1985 (Box 2)
  - Computer files, 8 computer media (Box 2)
  - The LGBT-CRC New Student Orientation, 2002; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (Box 2)
  - Gays and Lesbians in the Residences, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - BioSci 199: Transgender Issues. Readings, Spring 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Queer Issues '99: Alternative Spring Break. Reader (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Email correspondence 6/1/85-5/1/86 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Email correspondence10/15/84 – 5/31/85 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Email correspondence4/22/84 - 09/6/84 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fire! – LGBT newsletter 2000-2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Unsorted photo submissions and other records of Masque (publication) (Box 4)
  - Binder: GLAS Scrapbook Oct. 1986-Sept. 1987 (flyers, announcements, clippings, press releases, stationery, and 3 photos) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Binder: GPU at Stanford Scrapbook Vol. II 1974-76 (newsletters, flyers, clippings, calendars, etc., with a few dating from 1979-87) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Binder: GPU at Stanford Scrapbook Vol. III 1976-78 (newsletters, flyers, press releases, clippings, calendars, and transcription of talk by R. G. Hamerton-Kelly at 75th Anniversary of the Dedication of Memorial Church) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Binder: Exhibit notes from LGBT's 30th Anniversary Exhibit 2004 (includes DVDs of interview footage used for "Out on the Farm") (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2008-072
  - Stanford Cares: Community Response – program for memorial service and concert, Feb. 18, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Names Project – letter and two photos (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Remembrances of those who've died:
    - Esquibel, Richard (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Howard, Donald R. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Koloski, Martin G. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - McNaughton, Duffy (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Gerald (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Peterson, Michael (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Rogers, J. C. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Smillie, Baxter (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Spears, Jay (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Thompson, David (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Trowbridge, John (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Vandenberg, J. Gregory (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Zambrano, Mark (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Roger [no last name] (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2008-206
  General note
  Volumes contain newsletters, clippings, flyers, other printed materials, and photographs.